youtele.com 2011-05-30

# YOU Broadband & Cable India Limited: Leading High Speed Broadband Internet Service provider in India. Super Fast Connection.

| Privacy  
---  
What This Privacy Policy Covers  
  
  * This policy covers how YOU Broadband & Cable India Limited ("Company") treats personal information that the Company collects and receives, including information related to your past use of the Company's products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number etc.

**Information Collection and Use**  
**General**

  * The Company collects personal information when you register with the Company , when you use the Company products or services, when you visit the Company pages or the pages of certain partners of the Company. The Company may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. The Company shall have the right pass on the same to its business associates, franchisees without referring the same to you.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with the Company and sign in to our services, you become our valued customer.
  * The Company collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. 
  * The Company can use information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * The Company may share personal information about you with other people under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with the Company under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help the Company communicate with you about offers from the Company and our marketing partners.
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Company's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another company under a diffferent management. In this event, the Company will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * The Company plans to display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * The Company will not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. . 
  * The Company works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and service providers in many different industries and categories of business.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Company's service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Company's Newsletter, that are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
The Company may update this policy and display the same in their website without notice to you and such posting will be deemed to have been read by you.  
  
|   
---  
YOU Broadband & Cable India Limited  
  
"YOU Broadband & Cable India Limited ("Company"), is proposing, subject to statutory and/or regulatory requirements, market conditions and other considerations, an initial public offer of its equity shares ("Equity Shares") of face value Rs. 10/- each and has filed a draft red herring prospectus ("DRHP") with the Securities & Exchange Board of India ("SEBI") in connection therewith. The DRHP is available on the website of SEBI at [www.sebi.gov.in](http://www.sebi.gov.in/), on the website of the Book Running Lead Manager, Edelweiss Capital Limited, at [www.edelcap.com](http://www.edelcap.com/). This advertisement does not constitute or form part of any offer or invitation to sell or issue, or any solicitation of any offer to purchase or subscribe for, any Equity Shares. Any potential investor should note that an investment in the Equity Shares involves a high degree of risk. For details, potential investors should refer to the DRHP filed with the SEBI including the section titled "Risk Factors". This material is not an offer of securities for sale in the United States or elsewhere. The Equity Shares are not being registered under the U.S. Securities Act of 1933, as amended (the "U.S. Securities Act"), or any U.S. state securities laws, and may not be offered or sold within the United States, except pursuant to an exemption from, or in a transaction not subject to, the registration requirements of the U.S. Securities Act and applicable U.S. state securities laws. There will be no public offering of the Equity Shares of the Company in the United States. This material may not be published or distributed in the United States, Canada, Japan or Australia."

< click here to read >
